{
    "subject": "Saeed_Akhtar_Mirza",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Mohan_Joshi_Hazir_Ho!",
    "human_readable": "Saeed Akhtar Mirza produced the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9164573550224304,
            "question": "What is the title of the film produced by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9060651063919067,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8796685338020325,
            "question": "Who produced the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.802747368812561,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Saeed Akhtar Mirza."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8005608320236206,
            "question": "Give an example of a film produced by Saeed Akhtar Mirza."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7907159328460693,
            "question": "Who created the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7601093649864197,
            "question": "Is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.754734218120575,
            "question": "Is Saeed Akhtar Mirza known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5836532711982727,
            "question": "What type of work did Saeed Akhtar Mirza create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.543428361415863,
            "question": "Who is the director of Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saeed Akhtar Mirza produced the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14539_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Saeed Akhtar Mirza create?",
            "html": "yago_14539_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Saeed Akhtar Mirza known for directing films?",
            "html": "yago_14539_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! a film?",
            "html": "yago_14539_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14539_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Saeed Akhtar Mirza as a filmmaker who produced and directed several notable films, including \"Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!\" (1984). Therefore, the statement that Saeed Akhtar Mirza produced the film \"Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}